Alexandra Campbell

1+ (602) 625-2503

email AlexandraBrinnCampbell@gmail.com

GitHub killeraliens

LinkedIn /alexandra-brinn-campbell

www killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn

Dedicated programmer coming from a background in industrial design and graphics. I love scripting digital experiences for people and can offer a range of both creative and technical skills. Always ready to work with any new tools for the iob.

Dev

JavaScript • React • Enzyme • jQuery • HTML5 • CSS/Sass • Bootstrap • Node.js • Ruby on Rails • SQL • PostgreSQL • MVC architecture • OOP • GitHub git • ZEIT now • Heroku

UX & UI

CSS Grid & Flexbox • responsive design •
Adobe Creative Suite • Webflow • Invision • Sketch •
Figma • Whimsical • Mindnode • AutoCad •
user interviews & testing • branding & creative content

Projects

Doctors Near Me | killeraliens.github.io/doctors-near-me

Doctors Near Me is an app that locates and displays medical professionals based on your location, insurance plan, or specialty search inputs. This project utilizes OOJS & constructor functions to pull doctor info from highly nested JSON objects, as well as ES 2017 features to sequence multiple API calls for its filter results.

HTML5 • CSS • jQuery • JavaScript • Better Doctor API • Google Maps JavaScript API • Google Geocoding • Reverse Geocoding APIs

Goat's Guide | www.goatsguide.com

Goat's Guide is a heavy metal event & venue database concept as well as an ongoing study in UX design. I am currently reworking this project using React, Express/Node to reduce app loading time, and encourage user participation with the integration of Facebook's Graph API.

Ruby on Rails • HTML-scraping • Watir • Nokogiri • background tasks • Sidekiq • Devise gem auth • PostgreSQL database • Heroku

You can find more projects on my website at killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn

Experience

Apr 2015 - Jul 2018

Burgeon Group | Design Project Manager | instagram @BurgeonGroup

- Managed projects through complete lifecycle by coordinating with stakeholders, including clients, designers, and fabrication departments.
- Supported spatial design, client communications and presentations, marketing content, and file management.
- Executed and presented technical drafting, construction & installation plan documents on a weekly basis.

2012 - 2015

Demi Coffee, Phoenix AZ | Owner | instagram @DemiCoffee

- Known in the community for a unique (tiny!) space, amazing cold brew, and attention to quality.
- Provided exceptional customer service and a niche experience with creative food, beverages and atmosphere.

2012 - Current

Curiotile | Design and Development

- A personal project which showcases knowledge on process, materials, and design.
- Iterative "flatpack" designs in stainless and powdercoat steel, custom displays & storage solutions.
- · Images & descriptions available on request.

2009 - 2013

Ah Diós I Freelance Graphics & Branding

- Collaborated with small team in the areas of web, film, branding, and UX design.
- Supported brand development through signage, web, and packaging graphics for Visual+Intent, Cartel Coffee Lab, Request Manufacturing, and Sooh Media.

Education

May 2019 - Curr

Thinkful. JavaScript, Node Fullstack Engineering Program

Jan - Mar 2019

Le Wagon, London. Ruby on Rails Coding Bootcamp

Feb - Mar 2018

General Assembly 8 week course in UX design

BDES Industrial Design, 2007

Emily Carr University, Vancouver BC